certainteed.com 2019-07-18

# Legal - Privacy Policy | CertainTeed

**Effective Date: February 2018**

CertainTeed Corporation and its North American affiliates, including without limitation CertainTeed Ceilings Corporation, CertainTeed Gypsum, Inc., CertainTeed Canada Gypsum, Inc., and CertainTeed Canada, Inc. (collectively, the "Company") respect your privacy. We have adopted the following policies and procedures to ensure that any information you provide to us on the CertainTeed Web Site and the CertainTeed Connect Web Site (the "Site") is treated appropriately and with your full knowledge and consent. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to explain what information we may collect from you and how this information may be used.

**What type of personal information is collected on this Site and how is it used?**

Certain areas of the Site may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. These requests are limited to specific activities on the Site where the use of such information is necessary such as to process an online transaction or respond to a request for product literature or send your contact information to a service professional of your choosing. Your participation in these activities is completely optional.

  * **Requests for Literature or Other Information**. In many cases we offer additional information about the products and services described on the Site. To request this information, you must supply us with certain contact information such as your name, mailing address and email address. 
    * **Registration, Ordering and Transaction Information**. Certain transactional information must be supplied to the Company to permit access to the Site and to place an order such as your name, your company name, shipping address, email address and certain financial information (e.g., Purchase Order Number, Purchase Order Date). This information is used solely for permission to access the Site, order, billing and collection purposes. You may have an option to input certain materials or information, or otherwise communicate with the Company.  Information that you supply, or communications you may make to the Company, may include your name, city, state, zip code and email address, and information pertinent to your interests. The Company will use this information to assist you or improve its service to you.  The contact information may also be used by us in connection with certain marketing activities such as a promotion or new product announcements. The Company will refrain from making these types of communications to customers who have opted out of these programs as described further below.Customers can opt-out of these communications via their account preferences on the site, as well as in the e-mail communications. 
    * For additional information on opting-out of communications, customers may contact [CertainTeed.Connect@saint-gobain.com](mailto:CertainTeed.Connect@saint-gobain.com).

  * **Site Use Data.** The Company may also collect other information from customers and visitors to the Site such as the user’s IP address, domain name, length of time spent on the Site, and the pages accessed during each visit to the Site. The Company uses this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**How will the Company protect your personal information?**

We will not share your personal information with third parties (aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, that either are bound to comply with our Privacy Statement or have privacy policies that protect your information) without your permission.

Certain information supplied by you to our Site may be password-protected, and you should take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, remember to sign out and close your browser window when you finish accessing our Site in order to prevent others from accessing your personal information. You are solely responsible for the control and use of each password you create.

The Company may disclose information you have provided to us if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on the Company; or (2) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company.

If we gather demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income), we will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.

**What are "Cookies" and does this Site use them?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you would rather we not store the information for future use. Our cookies enable us to provide you with more personal service. The Company uses cookies to facilitate the administration of the Site and enhance the content of the Site for our users.  Detailed information about cookies can be found by visiting our cookie policy.

**What security measures are employed by this Site?**

The Company has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. We will protect the transmission of credit card and other transactional information through industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

**What about your links to other web sites? Is my information protected by these sites?**

This Site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. The Company encourages our users to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this Site. Additionally, the existence of any external link or external request for information does not suggest that we are endorsing the linked or external company or its products or services.

**Do Not Track**

The Site does not support Do Not Track at this time. Do Not Track is a privacy preference that you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across websites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For details, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit [www.donottrack.us](http://www.donottrack.us/).

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Company may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in its discretion. Company will post such changes to this web page and note the date of the most recent revision of the Privacy Policy above. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently to be informed of how Company is collecting, using, retaining, protecting, disclosing, and transferring your information. Your continued use of the Site after Company posts any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of such changes.

**Access to Your Personal Data; Questions and Comments**

We will provide you with reasonable access to your personal data in accordance with relevant laws, including by making reasonable efforts to provide you with the opportunity to update your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personal information. For any questions or comments about this privacy policy or your personal data, please send a written request to:  CertainTeed Corporation, Attn: CertainTeed Connect Customer Portal, 20 Moores Road, Malvern, PA 19355.

**A Special Note about Children**

This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. The Company does not intend to collect any personal information or data from individuals that identify themselves as children under the age of 13. If the Company becomes aware that information from a child under the age of 13 has been submitted to this Site, we will respond to the inquiry, and, when appropriate, delete all personally identifiable information (including email address) concerning that child from our records. That information will not be used for any other purpose, nor will it be disclosed to any other parties. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to this Site, you are encouraged to contact us via the Contact Us form on the site. We believe parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.

**Terms and Conditions of Use**

Your use of the Site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Statement and the Company’s Terms and Conditions of Use. By using this Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Statement and those Terms.
